// import shuffleArray from "../helpers/shuffleArray.js";

// import { getRandomItem } from "../helpers/shuffleAnswer.js";
// const getRandomItem = (array) =>
//   array[Math.floor(Math.random() * array.length)];

export const DrewBarrymoreQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Drew Barrymore play a girl who falls in love with a man with short-term memory loss?",
    options: [
      "50 First Dates",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "The Wedding Singer",
      "Fever Pitch",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "50 First Dates",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Drew Barrymore as a teacher who goes undercover as a high school student?",
    options: [
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Donnie Darko",
      "Whip It",
      "The Wedding Singer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Never Been Kissed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial*, what role does Drew Barrymore play?",
    options: ["Gertie", "Elliott", "Mary", "Janet"],
    correctAnswer: "Gertie",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which film stars Drew Barrymore as one of three detectives working for a mysterious boss?",
    options: [
      "Charlie's Angels",
      "Whip It",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Fever Pitch",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Charlie's Angels",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Wedding Singer*, who does Drew Barrymore's character plan to marry before realizing she loves the wedding singer?",
    options: ["Glen Gulia", "Billy Idol", "Sammy", "George"],
    correctAnswer: "Glen Gulia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Drew Barrymore as the girlfriend of a die-hard Boston Red Sox fan?",
    options: [
      "Fever Pitch",
      "50 First Dates",
      "Music and Lyrics",
      "He's Just Not That Into You",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Fever Pitch",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Donnie Darko*, what subject does Drew Barrymore's character teach?",
    options: ["English", "Math", "History", "Science"],
    correctAnswer: "English",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Whip It*, what sport does Drew Barrymore's character play?",
    options: ["Roller derby", "Soccer", "Baseball", "Tennis"],
    correctAnswer: "Roller derby",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Music and Lyrics*, what role does Drew Barrymore play alongside Hugh Grant?",
    options: ["Lyricist", "Singer", "Dancer", "Music producer"],
    correctAnswer: "Lyricist",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Drew Barrymore star as Cinderella in a historical retelling of the fairy tale?",
    options: [
      "Ever After",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Riding in Cars with Boys",
      "Charlie's Angels",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ever After",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Scream*, what happens to Drew Barrymore's character in the opening scene?",
    options: [
      "She is killed",
      "She escapes",
      "She hides",
      "She calls for help",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "She is killed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Drew Barrymore as the voice of a dog named Chloe?",
    options: [
      "Beverly Hills Chihuahua",
      "Cats & Dogs",
      "The Secret Life of Pets",
      "Bolt",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Beverly Hills Chihuahua",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which film does Drew Barrymore play a journalist covering a beauty pageant?",
    options: [
      "Miss You Already",
      "Confessions of a Dangerous Mind",
      "Lucky You",
      "Never Been Kissed",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Never Been Kissed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Firestarter*, what special ability does Drew Barrymore's character have?",
    options: ["Pyrokinesis", "Telekinesis", "Invisibility", "Mind control"],
    correctAnswer: "Pyrokinesis",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Drew Barrymore as a teenage girl with dreams of becoming a writer?",
    options: [
      "Riding in Cars with Boys",
      "The Wedding Singer",
      "Whip It",
      "50 First Dates",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Riding in Cars with Boys",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *50 First Dates*, what is the name of Drew Barrymore’s character?",
    options: ["Lucy", "Julia", "Josie", "Elle"],
    correctAnswer: "Lucy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Drew Barrymore alongside Cameron Diaz and Lucy Liu as secret agents?",
    options: ["Charlie's Angels", "Whip It", "Ever After", "Fever Pitch"],
    correctAnswer: "Charlie's Angels",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Drew Barrymore's character date a songwriter?",
    options: ["Music and Lyrics", "Fever Pitch", "50 First Dates", "Whip It"],
    correctAnswer: "Music and Lyrics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Wedding Singer*, what is Drew Barrymore's character's profession?",
    options: ["Waitress", "Teacher", "Journalist", "Lawyer"],
    correctAnswer: "Waitress",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Drew Barrymore as a mother struggling to balance her dreams and responsibilities?",
    options: [
      "Riding in Cars with Boys",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Whip It",
      "Ever After",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Riding in Cars with Boys",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Fever Pitch*, what sport is central to the plot?",
    options: ["Baseball", "Football", "Basketball", "Hockey"],
    correctAnswer: "Baseball",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Drew Barrymore as a woman who falls for a man she can't remember?",
    options: [
      "50 First Dates",
      "Music and Lyrics",
      "The Wedding Singer",
      "Never Been Kissed",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "50 First Dates",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Charlie's Angels: Full Throttle*, what is the name of Drew Barrymore's character?",
    options: ["Dylan", "Natalie", "Alex", "Kelly"],
    correctAnswer: "Dylan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Confessions of a Dangerous Mind*, what is Drew Barrymore's character's relationship to the main character?",
    options: ["Girlfriend", "Sister", "Co-worker", "Detective"],
    correctAnswer: "Girlfriend",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which film features Drew Barrymore as a writer named Sophie Fisher?",
    options: [
      "Music and Lyrics",
      "Fever Pitch",
      "Ever After",
      "The Wedding Singer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Music and Lyrics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial*, what does Gertie, played by Drew Barrymore, dress E.T. as?",
    options: ["A woman", "A dog", "A ghost", "A pirate"],
    correctAnswer: "A woman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Drew Barrymore as a reluctant roller derby participant?",
    options: ["Whip It", "Fever Pitch", "50 First Dates", "Music and Lyrics"],
    correctAnswer: "Whip It",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *He's Just Not That Into You*, what role does Drew Barrymore play?",
    options: [
      "A media executive",
      "A teacher",
      "A doctor",
      "A fashion designer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A media executive",
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie features Drew Barrymore as a zombie mom?",
    options: [
      "Santa Clarita Diet",
      "Donnie Darko",
      "Riding in Cars with Boys",
      "Whip It",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Santa Clarita Diet",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Donnie Darko*, what book is Drew Barrymore's character passionate about?",
    options: [
      "The Destructors",
      "The Catcher in the Rye",
      "1984",
      "To Kill a Mockingbird",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Destructors",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which film features Drew Barrymore as a character who becomes best friends with her high school crush?",
    options: [
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "The Wedding Singer",
      "50 First Dates",
      "Riding in Cars with Boys",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Never Been Kissed",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Blended*, who plays Drew Barrymore's love interest?",
    options: [
      "Adam Sandler",
      "Ben Stiller",
      "Matthew McConaughey",
      "Hugh Grant",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Adam Sandler",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Drew Barrymore's character manage a chaotic radio station?",
    options: [
      "Home Fries",
      "Riding in Cars with Boys",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Charlie's Angels",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Home Fries",
  },
  {
    question: "In *The Stand In*, who does Drew Barrymore play?",
    options: [
      "A famous actress and her stand-in",
      "A police officer",
      "A teacher",
      "A wedding planner",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A famous actress and her stand-in",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Boys on the Side*, who does Drew Barrymore's character run away with?",
    options: [
      "Whoopi Goldberg and Mary-Louise Parker",
      "Jennifer Aniston and Courteney Cox",
      "Julia Roberts and Meg Ryan",
      "Demi Moore and Sharon Stone",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Whoopi Goldberg and Mary-Louise Parker",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Everyone Says I Love You*, what genre is the movie?",
    options: ["Musical", "Horror", "Science fiction", "Thriller"],
    correctAnswer: "Musical",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Perfect Catch*, what is Drew Barrymore’s character's profession?",
    options: ["Businesswoman", "Teacher", "Photographer", "Chef"],
    correctAnswer: "Businesswoman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Drew Barrymore play a princess in a modern-day fairy tale?",
    options: [
      "Ever After",
      "The Wedding Singer",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Whip It",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ever After",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Charlie's Angels*, what is Drew Barrymore's character's real name?",
    options: ["Helen Zaas", "Dylan Sanders", "Jane Foster", "Natalie Cook"],
    correctAnswer: "Dylan Sanders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Drew Barrymore as a woman facing a terminal illness?",
    options: [
      "Miss You Already",
      "Never Been Kissed",
      "Music and Lyrics",
      "Whip It",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Miss You Already",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Going the Distance*, what is the relationship between Drew Barrymore and Justin Long's characters?",
    options: [
      "Long-distance couple",
      "Siblings",
      "Co-workers",
      "Childhood friends",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Long-distance couple",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Duplex*, what problem do Drew Barrymore's character and her husband face?",
    options: [
      "An obnoxious neighbor",
      "A haunted house",
      "A legal battle",
      "A troubled marriage",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "An obnoxious neighbor",
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie features Drew Barrymore as an undercover FBI agent?",
    options: [
      "Charlie's Angels",
      "Whip It",
      "Miss You Already",
      "The Stand In",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Charlie's Angels",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Grey Gardens*, who does Drew Barrymore portray?",
    options: [
      "Little Edie",
      "Jackie Kennedy",
      "Princess Diana",
      "Marilyn Monroe",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Little Edie",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Fever Pitch*, who plays Drew Barrymore's love interest?",
    options: ["Jimmy Fallon", "Adam Sandler", "Ben Stiller", "Hugh Grant"],
    correctAnswer: "Jimmy Fallon",
  },
];

export default DrewBarrymoreQuestions;
